<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) 2017 Razeware LLC

  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
  of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
  in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
  to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
  copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
  furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
  all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
  IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
  FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
  AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
  LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
  OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
  THE SOFTWARE.
  -->
<resources>
  <array name="images">
    <item>@drawable/cereal_guy</item>
    <item>@drawable/f_yeah</item>
    <item>@drawable/forever_alone</item>
    <item>@drawable/freddie_mercury</item>
    <item>@drawable/lol_guy</item>
    <item>@drawable/neil_degrasse_tyson</item>
    <item>@drawable/oh_crap</item>
    <item>@drawable/okay</item>
    <item>@drawable/rage_guy</item>
    <item>@drawable/troll_face</item>
    <item>@drawable/y_u_no_guy</item>
    <item>@drawable/yao_ming</item>
  </array>

  <string-array name="names">
    <item>Cereal Guy</item>
    <item>F!@# Yeah</item>
    <item>Forever Alone</item>
    <item>Freddie Mercury</item>
    <item>LOL Guy</item>
    <item>Neil deGrasse Tyson</item>
    <item>Oh Crap/OMG Face</item>
    <item>Okay Guy</item>
    <item>Rage Guy</item>
    <item>Trollface/Problem?</item>
    <item>"Y U No" Guy</item>
    <item>Yao Ming Face</item>
  </string-array>

  <string-array name="descriptions">
    <item>Cereal Guy is a stick figure character commonly used on image boards and discussion forums as a multi-purpose reaction face.</item>
    <item>F!@# Yeah is a series of four-pane cartoon strips featuring a stick figure looking rather self-complacent and quite frankly, for all the right reasons. Originally posted via /b/ board on February 11, 2010, these cartoons illustrate all sorts of triumphant moments in our daily lives that make us feel awesome, like when you wake up a few seconds before the morning alarm goes off. This phenomenon can be also seen as the antithesis to Rageguy comics, another four-pane series originating from 4chan circa late 2008.</item>
    <item>Forever Alone is an exploitable rage comic character that is used to express loneliness and disappointment with life. The face has also been used as an advice animal and inspired the creation of the snowclone template \"Forever an X.\"</item>
    <item>Freddie Mercury Rage Pose is a rage comic character made from a photo of deceased British musician and former lead vocalist for the rock band Queen Freddie Mercury. The image is typically used to indicate that an extraordinary feat has been accomplished, similar to the F!@# Yea illustration.</item>
    <item>LOL Guy is a rage comic character that is often used to indicate laughter and general amusement.</item>
    <item>Neil deGrasse Tyson Reaction is a rage comic character and reaction face of astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson making a defensive gesture. The character image is sometimes associated with the catchphrase "Watch out guys, we’re dealing with a badass over here" that is used to mock arrogant and boastful statements made by Internet users.</item>
    <item>The Oh Crap or OMG Face refers to an exploitable image used in rage comics to express an array of feelings including astonishment, revelation, or sheer rage. It is often paired with red or white text, summing up the character\'s thoughts. It is also used to represent a Gropaga, or follower of Inglip.</item>
    <item>Okay Guy is a sullen-looking rage comic character who is accompanied by the caption \"okay.\" The face is often used in the final panel of comics meant to convey a feeling of hopeless resignation.</item>
    <item>The name Rageguy refers to the main character of a series of crudely-drawn comics typically consisting of four panes, portraying situations which can bring rage and exasperation, with the main character screaming with anger as a result. Due to its simplicity and exploitability, Rageguy has been proven popular thus being evolved into a comic series now known as Rage Comics.</item>
    <item>Trollface is a rage comic character wearing a mischievous smile that is meant to represent the facial expression of an Internet troll. The image is most commonly used to portray a character as a troll in rage comics, or alternatively, to identify oneself or another participant as such in online discussions.</item>
    <item>\"Y U NO\" Guy (also known as \"Y U No [X]?\") is an image macro series using SMS shorthands and carefree grammar as a way to bring someone’s attention on a particular subject or issue. The unique facial expression worn by stick-figure character is believed to have been traced from the Japanese sci-fi manga / anime series Gantz.</item>
    <item>Yao Ming Face (sometimes referred to as “F!@# That Guy” or “Dumb B!@#$”) is a rage comic-style contour drawing of the professional basketball player Yao Ming wearing a hearty smile. The image is typically used as a reaction face to convey a dismissive attitude towards someone else’s input in online discussions, then usually following something that one ups their input.</item>
  </string-array>

  <string-array name="urls">
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/cereal-guy</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/fck-yea</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/forever-alone</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/freddie-mercury-rage-pose</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/lol-guy</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/neil-degrasse-tyson-reaction</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/oh-crap-omg-rage-face</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/okay-guy</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/rage-guy-fffffuuuuuuuu</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/trollface-coolface-problem</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/y-u-no-guy</item>
    <item>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/yao-ming-face-bitch-please</item>
  </string-array>
</resources>